[Family Safe](https://toomics.com/en/help/private_terms)_Close_

Become a member now and enjoy 50,000+ episodes!

Sign in

* [_Gender_
    
    Unknown](javascript:;)
* [_Language_
    
    English](javascript:;)

dropdown menu

#### Language

English

中文(简体)

中文(繁體)

Español(LA)

Español(ES)

Italiano

Português

Deutsch

Français

日本語

Close OK

#### Gender

Male

Female

Unknown

Close OK

#### VIP Membership reactivated

OK

#### You have received a 1 month VIP Membership for free!

You can cancel your VIP Membership again at any time after 2 weeks.

OK

#### My Coins

Web Coins

0

App Coins

0

Bonus Coins

0

Gift Coins

0

Close [Purchase Coins](https://toomics.com/en/mypage/payment/type/payment-plan)

#### Pick Your Genres!

##### Tell us what you like!

You can change your favorite genres again later.

Are you over 18?

* * *

 Select All

* Drama
    
* Romance
    
* School life
    
* Comedy
    
* Fantasy
    
* Action
    
* BL
    
* Horror
    
* Thriller
    
* Sci-fi
    
* Historical

Choose three or more of your favorite genres!

Cancel OK

Customer Service
================

Do you need help?

Privacy Policy
==============

**Privacy Policy**

Toomics Co., Ltd and Toomics Global UK Limited (hereinafter “Toomics”, “the company”, “we”, “us”, “our”) values your privacy rights and protects the personal information collected, stored, and used in connection with Toomics Service(“Service”). Hence, we developed a Privacy Policy that covers how we collect, store and use your information.

What & How We Collect Information

What We Collect

We collect the following information to help you create your account, provide customer service, and various services.

\- When creating an account –

Essential information needed to create an account such as social ID, Nickname, e-email, encoded password and etc.

\- When making a purchase –

For credit card : credit card company, credit card number and etc.

For credit transfer : name of the bank, account number and etc.

\- When using the Service –

Means of register, date of register, IP Address, cookie, date of visit, service usage record, malfunction record, device information and etc.

How We Collect

We collect your information in the following way.

\- Through our webpage, call, customer service, e-mail, events and promotions

\- Provided by partner companies

\- Through data collection tools

Collecting Personal Information & Its Purpose

We collect information when you use our Service to provide, maintain, improve, develop our Service, to track and block illegal users, to protect the Service users, and to provide advertisements with high relevance to users.

Sharing & Provision of Personal Information

We use personal information of users within the scopes mentioned in “Collecting Personal Information & Its Purpose”. We do not use personal information of users beyond those scopes without the consent of users, or share with external parties. However, for social log-in, we may share information in order to process social log-in.

Consignment of Personal Information Processing

We consign personal information to the following companies to improve our Service. We have clearly stipulated in a consignment agreement according to related laws to safely manage personal information. The following are consignees and their purpose.

​

|     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Consignee | Entrusted Task | Personal Information Retention and Use Period |
| EXIMBAY / PayLetter / OnePaid / Paymentwall / Checkout.com | Processing Transactions | Until the account is terminated or termination of the consignment contract |
| IOS In app purchase | Processing Transactions |
| Android In app purchase | Processing Transactions |

Personal Information Retention & Use Period

In principle, we immediately destroy the personal information of users once the purpose of personal information collection is achieved. However, certain information will be retained up to 5 years for management purposes.

Company Policy for Retention of Personal Information

\- Illegal Uses(Record of abnormal service usages such as illegal sign ups)

Items retained : e-mail, phone number used for sign up

Purpose of retention : to prevent illegal sign up and usage

Period of retention : 1 year

Technical and Administrative Security for Personal Information

We aim to maintain technical and administrative securities for your personal information to prevent loss, theft, leakage, alteration, or damage of your personal information.

Encoding Passwords

Toomics users’ passwords are encoded, and therefore only you know the password. Only you can access and change personal information.

Measures Against Hacking

We aim to protect your personal information from hacking and computer viruses to prevent leakage or damage of personal information.

To prevent your personal information from being damaged, we back-up our data regularly, and transfer personal information through encoded networks.

We take measures to stop and monitor breaches by using a firewall system and other technology.

**Disputes**

We will take appropriate measures to resolve any issue, claim, or dispute between you and Toomics that arises in whole or in part from the Service. 

If the dispute between you and Toomics is not resolved, it will be submitted, commenced, and be heard in “Seoul District Court” of the Republic of Korea. The laws of the Republic of Korea will govern any dispute of any sort that might arise between you and Toomics, except for the case when the unresolved issue, claim, or dispute between you and Toomics related or connected to your payment processed by Checkout.com. In this case, the resolution of your issue, claim, or dispute will be governed by the laws of United Kingdom, and will be submitted, commenced, and heard in the court of United Kingdom.

**Remove your data from Toomics**​

If you want to delete all your personal data Toomics has stored on you, Please send a request email to en.help@toomicsglobal.com including your name, email address and phone number.

We will respond promptly within 7 days of receiving your request for deletion of personal data. 

Contact Information Regarding Privacy Policy

If you have any questions regarding the Privacy Policy, please e-mail us at en.help@toomicsglobal.com 

Provision

**These Terms were last modified on Sep 28, 2021** 

**We value your privacy at Toomics Global.** Close

Toomics Global uses cookies to personalize your experience, to show you ads based on your interests, and for measurements and analytics purposes. By using our website and services, you agree to our use of cookies as described in our [Privacy Policy](https://toomics.com/en/help/private_terms)

Language

Toomics content are all protected by Copyright Law. Any unauthorized use, sharing or duplication may be punished by copyright laws.

Toomics Global Co.,Ltd. | E-mail : en.help@toomicsglobal.com

[* facebookToomics  
    Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/ToomicsWorld/)[* instagramToomics  
    Instagram](https://www.instagram.com/toomics.en/)

* Sign in
* Sign up

Sign up and read

**more episodes**

#### Sign in with social network

Recently used to sign in

##### _OR_

Sign in with email

Recent sign in

Number of sign in attempts left (/10) You've exceeded your maximum number of sign in attempts. (10 times)

Your password has been reset to protect your personal information.

Please reset your password or send an inquiry to [en.help@toomicsglobal.com](mailto:en.help@toomicsglobal.com).

 Keep me signed in [Forgot password?](https://toomics.com/en/auth/forgot_password)

Reset password   Sign in

Recent sign in

##### _Sign in with Social Media_

Recently used to sign in

#### Sign up with social network

##### _OR_

Sign up with email

By signing up, you agree to our  
[Terms of use](https://toomics.com/en/help/access_terms) & [Privacy Policy](https://toomics.com/en/help/private_terms).

By signing up, you agree to our  
[Terms of use](https://toomics.com/en/help/access_terms) & [Privacy Policy](https://toomics.com/en/help/private_terms).

Sign up

#### An email verification link  
has been sent

If you did not receive the email,  
Please check your Spam/Junk folder or click Resend.

Resend

##### _Sign up with Social Media_

close

Close

Same email found

#### The email you provided already has accounts tied to it.

Would you like to sign in to an account you already made or make a new account?

##### Your pre-existing accounts

Close

Close

Please verify your email address.

#### A verification email has been sent to  
  
Please enter the Code provided in  
the email to verify your email address.

##### Verification Code:

Verify

Don't see the email? [Resend](javascript:;)

### Please select your gender.

We will recommend contents that  
we think you may like.

*  [ Male](javascript:void(0))
*  [ Unknown](javascript:void(0))
*  [ Female](javascript:void(0))

close

#### "" accounts can only be signed up with Yahoo social media accounts.

##### _with social media_

####  Age Verification

Family safe mode is enabled, so you are unable to access our restricted contents.  
You need to confirm that you are over the age of 18 to turn off family safe mode.  

**Are you over the age of 18?**

### An email verification link  
has been sent

If you did not receive the email,  
Please check your Spam/Junk folder or click Resend.

Resend
